#### **ABOUT ME**

A demand generation, lifecycle, and marketing ops professional with 12+ years of experience across B2C and B2B tech companies. Looking for a senior marketing position where I can make the most impact.

Soft Skills	Hard Skills	Software
People management	Forecasting & planning	Google Suite
Hiring & developing	Demand generation	Salesforce
Strong presentation &	Product marketing	Marketo & Braze
communication experience	Sales & marketing ops	Mode & Looker
	Analytics: SQL, Excel	Outreach

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Co-Founder, StandardCode (YC Summer 2021)

May 2021 - May 2022

Founded StandardCode and went through the Summer 2021 batch of Y Combinator. We focused on creating an API that helped companies comply with child data privacy laws around the world. We successfully raised a \$2MM+seed round and had a few beta customers before pivoting based on market feedback. We explored other ideas including a financial savings product for teens as well as a tool for Customer Success and Sales to be faster at outbound prospecting.

#### Head of B2B Marketing, Remind

December 2015 - May 2021

Remind is the largest communication platform in K-12, funded by First Round Capital, Social + Capital, and Kleiner Perkins.

Started as a Senior Product Marketing Manager working on our first monetization efforts. Responsibilities included positioning, branding, GTM launch, and pricing. Our enterprise product, focused on school and district administrator tools gained traction and I was promoted to Head of B2B Marketing to focus on growth. I built a team and process around GTM for our enterprise offering. Responsibilities included building and scaling a demand generation engine, hiring and training our first SDRs, BDRs, and account executives, developing lifecycle marketing, and building our marketing and sales ops infrastructure. Grew from \$0 to \$20MM ARR.

## Growth & Product Projects, HireReady

February 2015 - December 2015

Worked on two entrepreneurial projects as founder that scaled to a few thousand users. HireReady was the common app for the gig economy. Clients included Homejoy, Flour & Water, Kokio food truck. Stork was a text-based Q&A service for expecting parents to connect with doulas, nurses, and lactation consultants.

# Growth Manager, Homejoy (acquired by Google)

December 2012 - February 2015

Homejoy is a home services marketplace funded by Y Combinator, Google Ventures, and Redpoint Ventures.

Joined Homejoy as the 2nd full-time employee. Launched 30 markets in 18 months. Started out as a city launcher, growing supply and demand in each of the first 20 U.S. markets before hiring a team under me to open the rest. Transitioned to a growth position where I created our lifecycle and retention programs for our demand and supply side using Oracle's Responsys.

# Business Development Manager, Nutraclick

January 2010 - September 2012

Nutraclick is one of the largest online direct response marketing companies selling health and beauty products.

Owned the P&L for one of Nutraclick's flagship brands, Force Factor. Responsibilities included supply chain management, product development, and contract negotiations with GNC, Bodybuilding.com, Walmart, and Walgreens. Launched 5 products with online and in–store distribution from formulation to promotion.

### EDUCATION Alum Bachelor of Science

Y Combinator Computational Biology

Summer '21 Massachusetts Institute of Technology

### **REFERENCES**